Guide to the Mark D. Weiser Papers, 1969-1999
Department of Special Collections
- Series 7. Talks
  - '94 SIGCSE Tech Symposium, Phoenix, Arizona, 1994 Mar. 10 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Platform talk given to senior staff, 1994 Mar. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Ubicomp presentation to Silicon Graphics, Inc., 1994 Apr. 12 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - CS Dept. at Brown University, Providence, Rhode Island, 1994 Apr. 26 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - John Seely Brown "Research strategies for the 90's", 1994 May 4 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Dealer transparencies: contracting, 1994 May 11 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Contracting for research in Xerox, 1993, 1994 May 11 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Poznan, Poland. 14th International Conference - Distributed Computer Systems, 1994 June 23 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Education in the 21st Century / Mark Weiser. CRA Snowbird Conference, 1994 July 11 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Scientist - scientist [1 of 2], 1994 Aug. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Scientist - scientist [2 of 2], 1994 Aug. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Ubiquitous Computing World Economic Forum, 1994 Sept. 20 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - PC Dealer, 1994 Oct. 11 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - PC Challenge double Dealer - Dealer, 1994 Oct. 11 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Building invisible technology, 1994 Oct. 18 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Swedish Royal Academy. Building invisible technology, 1994 Oct. 21 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - The Information Ho Chi Minh Trail [transparencies] / Steve McGeady, CMU, 1994 Oct. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - The Information Ho Chi Minh Trail [print-out] / Steve McGeady, CMU, 1994 Oct. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, 1994 Oct. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - JSB talk - Everyday computing, [1994?] (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Systems issues in mobile computing / presented by Douglas B. Terry, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - ISAT, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - John Seely Brown's University of Michigan talk transparencies: Computing & the knowledge economy, ca. 1994 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - UCO project review, 1995 Mar. 20 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Institute talk, 1995 Apr. 21 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - XRCC talk about C.S., 1995 Apr. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Tacit talk, 1995 May 25 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Talk to Air Force, 1995 July 6 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Timex [transparencies], 1995 July 18 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Timex [print-out], 1995 July 18 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - ESMS employee satisfaction measurement system, ca. 1995 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Huntington job at a top research laboratory, Berkeley, 1995 Fall (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - HP IT personal computer operating system strategy / presented by Robert James, 1996 Feb. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Tacit talk, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Tacit talk: supporting information, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Tacit talk: Tacit notes return to Mark Weiser, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Tacit talk: FX Minder, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Tacit talk: Minder sketches, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Tacit talk: [Timex Datalink Watch], 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Tacit talk: Related product, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Tacit talk: diba, 1996 pre-Mar. (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Intel Talk, 1996 May 1 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - PC TechForum, 1996 May (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Computer Science Challenges of the next 10 years, 1996 June 14 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Tacit CIC presentation, 1996 June 19 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - FX, 1996 June 20 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - IBM PC division presentation, 1996 June (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Talk to Jasons, 1996 June (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Talk to Defense Logistics, 1996 July 10 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Sharp, 1996 July (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Xerox Internet Task Force, 1996 July (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Warburg Pincus, [1996 Sept. 9] (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - O.C.T. Whistle, 1996 Sept. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Weiser Forum [1 of 2], 1996 Sept. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Weiser Forum [2 of 2], 1996 Sept. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Talk for "Leveraging cyberspace" conference, [1996 Oct. 8-9] (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Xerox's handheld future, Lesko, 1996 Oct. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Myercough remnants, ca. 1996 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Naval Graduate Center, ca. 1996 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Ubi Room, ca. 1996 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - JSB slides "Rethinking corporate research", Airforce, 1997 Jan. 16 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Air Force, 1997 Jan. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - TDMB, 1997 Jan. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Displays for Ubiquitous Computing, 1997 Mar. 18 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Infospecial, 1997 Mar. 20 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - John Seely Brown story of PARC, 1997 Mar. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Docuworld '97, 1997 May 13 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Docuworld: Documents & the Internet, 1997 May (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Software engineering, 1997 May (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Extra slides: Japan, 1997 June (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Japan, PARC & Ubi, 1997 June (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Thoman PDR [Enabling the Digital Document Experience] EDE talk, 1997 Aug. 4 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - NT at PARC, 1997 Aug. 27 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - P & G talk, 1997 Aug. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Thoman [Enabling the Digital Document Experience], 1997 Aug. (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Ars Electronica, 1997 Sept. 9 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Info Tech Challenges of Ten Years, 1997 Sept. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Inventories dinner slides, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Hyperbolic browser, 1997 Dec. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Fostering creativity: Japan, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Ubiquitous Computing, Future Trends, Navy [Information and Computing Futures], 1997 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified talk, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Virtual diplomacy, ca. 1997 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - MEMS course - extra 1 - production challenges, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - MEMS course - extra 2 - hinges, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - MEMS course - Part 1 - Intro, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - MEMS course - Part 2 - non-surface, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - MEMS course - Part 3 - surface MEMS intro, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - MEMS course - Part 4 - MUMPS process, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - MEMS course - Part 6 - CAD library, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - MEMS course - Part 7 - LEDIT tools, [1998 Jan. 6] (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Bali President's forum, 1998 Feb. 22 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Press briefing overview: Germany, 1998 Feb. 24-25 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Sonoma State [Information Technology Challenges of the Next Ten Years], 1998 Mar. 19 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Adobe talk, 1998 May 3 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Brazil talk, 1998 May (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Tech transfer talk, 1998 Nov. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified talk, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - ACM talk, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - The digital frontier and the future of documents - slides [1 of 2], n.d. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - The digital frontier and the future of documents - slides [2 of 2], n.d. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Displays for Ubi-SID, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Distributed: Operating Systems computer programming, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Editor talk, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Embodied virtuality [transparencies], n.d. (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Embodied virtuality [transparencies], n.d. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Extra slides, n.d. Aug. (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - FX / XL / Sharp, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Industrial / Academic relations, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Ineffable talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Info Tech (Librarians), n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - JSB [John Seely Brown] talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Lab history, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Marvin Theimer Ubi Comp talk to Carnegie Mellon, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Window System, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - NASA workstations talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - NOW, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - NSF / CER, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Omron, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - PARC overview (slides from M. Bernstein), n.d. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - PC Tech Forum, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Presentation to Defense Logistics Agency, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Prototype talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Prototyping, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Radio talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Rochester talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Seville Ubi talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Slides from unidentified talk, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Snowbird [Education for the Computer Science Community], n.d. (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - A study of programming problem representation in novie and expert programmers / Joan Shertz & Mark Weiser, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Shertz data, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Sweden presentation, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - System 33, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - System 33 for Glavin, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - System landscaping for programming environments, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - UMIACS talk: transparencies, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Untitle talk, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - What will change the way we communicate?, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - What will change the way we communicate?, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Xerox university grants program, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Xerox FGA slides, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Series 8. Travel files
  This series contains itineraries, notes, correspondence, and tourist literature collected by Mark Weiser on his various travels. Usually but not exclusively related to his scheduled Talks, these files often supplement the material in the Talks series.
  - UniForm Conference, 1984 Jan. 18-20 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - NSF / CER awardee conference, Utah, 1984 Feb. 22-24 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Mt. Kisco, 1984 Apr. 9-11 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - USENIX conference, 1984 June 12-16 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - NSF CER grantees annual meeting, 1985 Mar. 6-8 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - COMPCON conference - ZMOB computer (San Francisco, Calif.), 1985 Mar. 26-27 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Palo Alto (XEROX grantee meeting), 1985 May 7-11 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Palo Alto, 1985 July (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Los Alamos Computer Software Performance Symposium, 1985 Aug. 1-5 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - England 8th International Conference on Software Engineering, 1985 Aug. 15-30 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Palo Alto (University grant program - Xerox), 1985 Aug. 27-28 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Unix Advisory Panel, 1985 Oct. 2-5 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - 10th ACM (Orca Island, Washington), 1985 Dec. (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - NSF / CER conference, 1986 Mar. 16-18 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - CHI, 1986 Apr. 1 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Sun Users Group board meeting, 1986 June 25-27 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Palo Alto - Xerox, 1986 July (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Rochester, New York (invited to talk at Xerox), 1986 Sept. 14-15 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Sun Users Group conference, Washington, D.C., 1986 Oct. 6-8 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco, Calif. (Mark, Vicky, and the kids), 1986 Oct. 17-23 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Sun Users Group board meeting (Palo Alto, Calif.), 1986 Dec. 3-12 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Japan [1 of 4], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Japan [2 of 4], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Japan [3 of 4], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Japan [4 of 4], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Japan - miscellaneous [1 of 3], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Japan - miscellaneous [2 of 3], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Japan - miscellaneous [3 of 3], 1992 June (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Mark Weiser expense reports [1 of 2], 1992 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Mark Weiser expense reports [2 of 2], 1992 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Ubicom workshop, 1993 Apr. 5-6 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - CICSR Distinguished Lecture series, 1993 Nov. 18 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - AAAS Computer Conference, 1993 Dec. 17-19 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - SIAM conference, 1994 Feb. 15-17 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Distributed Systems conference [1 of 2], 1994 June 23 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Distributed Systems conference [2 of 2], 1994 June 23 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - CPA Snowbird conference, 1994 July 10-12 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Wireless and low power systems principal investigators meeting, 1994 July 24-26 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Active badge filming, 1994 Aug. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Scientist to scientist colloquium, 1994 Aug. 14-19 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - ISAT conference, 1994 Aug. 22-27 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - World Economic Forum, 1994 Sept. 20 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Royal Swedish Academy of Engineering Sciences, 1994 Oct. 21 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - UIST Conference, 1994 Nov. 2-4 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - CBA meeting, 1994 Nov. 3-4 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - United Methodist Church, 1994 Nov. 4 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Center for Telecommunications, 1994 Nov. 9 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Comdex conference, 1994 Nov. 14-15 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Intel, 1994 Nov. 28 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Personal Computer Outlook Conference, 1994 Dec. 6 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - CRA meeting, 1994 Dec. 15-16 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - New conference, 1995 Jan. 11-13 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - PDA Forum, 1995 Jan. 11-12 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Usenix conference, 1995 Jan. 18 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Intel meeting, 1995 Feb. 21 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Agents of Change conference, 1995 Apr. 20-22 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Microsoft Show, 1995 Apr. 27 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - CSIS conference [1 of 2], 1995 May 8-10 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - CSIS conference [2 of 2], 1995 May 8-10 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Naval Academy, 1995 May 24 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - SOSP meeting, 1995 June 13 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - SOSP Committee addresses and shipping orders, 1995 June 20 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - SOSP log of papers, 1995 June 20 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - SOSP general information, 1995 July 10 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - CSTO Joint PI meeting, 1995 July 10-13 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Timex meeting / Gary Schwartz / M. Myers, 1995 July 17-19 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Agenda 1996, 1995 Sept. 30 - Oct. 4 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - SOSP conference, 1995 Dec. (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - SOSP release forms, 1996 Jan. 8 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Nomadic conference, 1996 Mar. 15 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - World Economic Forum, 1996 Mar. 20 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - X2000, 1996 Mar. 21-22 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Document systems and services presentation, 1996 May 6 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, 1996 June 12-18 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - JASON Program, Mitre Corp., 1996 June 26 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - CRA, Snowbird, 1996 July 14 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - R.R. Donneley - Executive conference room, 1996 July 26 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications board meeting, Washington, D.C. [1 of 2], 1996 Aug. 21-23 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications board meeting, Washington, D.C. [2 of 2], 1996 Aug. 21-23 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - White space workshop, 1996 Aug. 26-27 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Leveraging cyberspace, 1996 Oct. 8 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - IEEE (did not go), 1996 Oct. 17 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - World Economic Forum, 1997 Jan. 30 - Feb. 4 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - World Economic Forum, 1997 Jan. 30 - Feb. 4 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - World Economic Forum correspondence, 1997 Jan. 30 - Feb. 4 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - World Economic Forum logistics, 1997 Jan. 30 - Feb. 4 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - World Economic Forum meetings / dinners, 1997 Jan. 30 - Feb. 4 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Peace Institute, 1997 Mar. 3 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - ACM conference, 1997 Mar. 3-6 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - CHI 97 & PC Forum, Atlanta/Tucson, 1997 Mar. 20-26 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - CHI 97, Atlanta, 1997 Mar. 23 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Highlands Forum (trip canceled), 1997 Apr. 1 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - The Arlington Institute, 1997 Apr. 25-28 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Docuworld, 1997 May 13-14 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - CSE, Boston, 1997 May 20-22 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Japan, 1997 June 9-13 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - NRC workshop, Berkeley, 1997 June 30 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Building market organizations course. Did not attend, 1997 July 7-9 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications [1 of 3], 1997 July 17 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications [2 of 3], 1997 July 17 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications [3 of 3], 1997 July 17 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - CESDIS meeting, Greenbelt, 1997 Aug. 8-12 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - ARS Electronica, Austria, 1997 Sept. 9-10 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Linz, 1997 Sept. 9-13 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - BMW, Monterey, Calif., 1997 Sept. 24-26 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Technical Manager's meeting - canceled, 1997 Sept. 26 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - MIT Wearables conference, 1997 Oct. 12-14 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - CSTB meeting, Washington, D.C. [1 of 2], 1997 Oct. 19-21 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - CSTB meeting, Washington, D.C. [2 of 2], 1997 Oct. 19-21 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Rochester conference, 1997 Oct. 29-30 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Hackers conference, 1997 Nov. 14-16 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - COMDEX Red Herring, 1997 Nov. 16-18 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - MEMS class, North Carolina, 1997 Dec. 2-4 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory trip, 1997 Dec. 9 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - SSQCG, Berkeley, 1998 Jan. 17-18 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Invites accepted, 1998 Jan. 21 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Declines, 1998 Jan. 31 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - DAVOS, 1998 Jan. 28 - Feb. 2 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - World Economic Forum, 1998 Jan. 29 - Feb. 3 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Bali Darmstadt Conference, Brazil [1 of 3], 1998 Feb. 17-26 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Bali Darmstadt Conference, Brazil [2 of 3], 1998 Feb. 17-26 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Bali Darmstadt Conference, Brazil [3 of 3], 1998 Feb. 17-26 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Bali trip, 1998 Feb. 19 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Bali, 1998 Feb. 19 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - ISAT - Palo Alto, 1998 Mar. 3-4 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Sonoma State University, 1998 Mar. 19 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - ISAT - Boston, 1998 Apr. 7-8 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Buildings workshop, Germany, 1998 Apr. 24-27 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - American Farm Bureau / Media Laboratory, 1998 Apr. 28 - May 3 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Brazil, 1998 May 11-15 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Toshiba - canceled, 1998 May 22 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - ISAT - did not attend, 1998 May 26-27 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - ITRD / CSTO, Irvine, Calif., 1998 June 7-9 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - MIT strategy meeting & SIGGRAPH, Boston & Orlando, 1998 July 22-23 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Snobird - cancelled, 1998 July 26-28 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Woods Hole ISAT - hotel cancelled, 1998 Aug. 17-21 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Woods Hole meeting, NAS/ITRD, 1998 Sept. 10-11 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - POP Books workshop, 1998 Sept. 14 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - DocuWorld, Seattle, 1998 Sept. 14-17 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Media Lab, Boston, 1998 Oct. 6-8 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Gartner Group Expo, Orlando, Florida, 1998 Oct. 14-15 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Knowwhere Corp., 1998 Nov. 4 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - PLOR, Nashville, 1998 Nov. 10-13 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - COMDEX, 1998 Nov. 16 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - BMW workshop, 1998 Nov. 18 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - CESDIS / USRA board meeting, Greenbelt, Maryland, 1998 Dec. 7 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Ph.D. exam, London, 1999 Jan. 21-24 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - NTCC, Los Angeles, 1999 Feb. 4 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - New Media conference, Berkeley - did not attend, 1999 Mar. 10 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - AIPA99 symposium - cancelled, 1999 Mar. 24 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - MIT Media Lab, Boston - cancelled, 1999 Apr. 5-7 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - WPI dinner - did not attend, 1999 Apr. 6 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - CSE Program review, San Diego - cancelled, 1999 Apr. 12-13 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Leadership Communications Forum, Rochester - did not attend, 1999 Apr. 20-21 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Embedded System Panel, San Jose - cancelled, 1999 May 5 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Hanover, Volkswagon, Germany - cancelled, 1999 May 7 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - IEEE Symposium, Oakland - did not attend, 1999 May 12 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Germany - Muenchner Kreis - did not attend, 1999 June 16 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - SAE conference, San Diego - did not attend, 1999 June 21-22 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Series 9. NASA Board files
  This series contains reports and memos gathered by Weiser in his role as a member of an advisory board to NASA.
  - CESDIS Science Council meeting, 1998 Dec. 7 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Universities Space Research Assocation copies / agreement, 1998 Aug. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - USRA - CESDIS Science Council, 1998 Aug. (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - USRA - CESDIS, 1997 Aug. 12 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Series 10. Conference materials and proceedings
  This series consists almost entirely of the printed proceedings of various conferences that Mark Weiser attended. Weiser presented papers or gave talks at many of these conferences, thus many of the publications in this series contain content by Weiser.
  - AAAS conference [1 of 3], 1993 Dec. 17-19 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - AAAS conference [2 of 3], 1993 Dec. 17-19 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - AAAS conference [3 of 3], 1993 Dec. 17-19 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - ACM conference proceedings, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - ACM international conference on software engineering, London, UK, 1985 Aug. 28-30 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - ACM operating systems review, vol. 26, no. 1, 1992 Jan. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - ACM proceedings of the ACM SIGPLAN SIGOA symposium on text manipulation, Portland, Oregon, 1981 June 8-10 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - ACM proceedings of the software quality and assurance workshop, 1978 Nov. 15-17 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - ACM CSC, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - ACM proceedings of the symposium on artificial intelligence and programming languages, 1977 Aug. 15-17 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - ACM proceedings of the workshop on data abstraction, databases, and conceptual modeling, 1980 June 23-26 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - ACM proceedings of the workshop on interface definition languages, 1994 Aug. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - ACM SIGART newsletter, no. 70, 1980 Feb. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - ACM SIGCOMM / SIGOPS interprocess communications workshop: proceedings, 1975 Mar. 24-25 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - ACM SIGOA conference on office information systems: proceedings, 1982 June 21-23 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - ACM SIGOIS conference on office information systems, 1986 Oct. 6-8 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - ACM SIGPLAN History of programming languages conference: preprints, 1993 Apr. 20-23 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - ACM SIGPLAN notices, Vol. 14, no. 6, 1979 June (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - ACM SIGPLAN workshop on languages, compilers, & tools for real-time systems: proceedings, 1995 June 21-22 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - ACM SIGSOFT '92: proceedings of the Fifth ACM SIGSOFT symposium on software development environments, 1992 Dec. 9-11 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - ACM SIGSOFT '94: proceedings of the Second ACM SIGSOFT symposium on foundations of software engineering, 1994 Dec. 6-9 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - ACM SIGSOFT '95: proceedings of the Third ACM SIGSOFT symposium on foundations of software engineering, 1995 Oct. 10-13 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - ACM SIGSOFT software engineering symposium: rapid prototyping. Columbia, Maryland, 1982 Apr. 19-21 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - ACM SIGSOFT / SIGPLAN software engineering symposium: high level debugging [1 of 3], 1983 Mar. 20-23 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - ACM SIGSOFT / SIGPLAN software engineering symposium: high level debugging [2 of 3], 1983 Mar. 20-23 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - ACM SIGSOFT / SIGPLAN software engineering symposium: high level debugging [3 of 3], 1983 Mar. 20-23 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - ACM symposium on operating systems principles, Copper Mountain Resort, Colorado, 1995 Dec. 3-6 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - ACM workshop on ubiquitous computing and augmented reality, M.I.T., 1993 Feb. 24-25 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - AFIPS conference proceedings, vol. 43, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - ACM 97 conference and exhibition, 1997 Mar. 1-4 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Agenda 97 conference proceedings, Scottsdale, Arizona, 1996 Oct. 19-22 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Ars Electronica festival, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Fourteenth Hawaii International Conference on System Sciences, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 1)